4 year old female hyena, born in spring, tan color, 70 pounds, from Friguia Park, Tunisia
12 year old male hyena, born in fall, brown color, 150 pounds, from Friguia Park, Tunisia
4 year old male hyena, born in spring, black color, 120 pounds, from Friguia Park, Tunisia
8 year old female hyena, unknown birth season, black and tan striped color, 105 pounds, from Friguia Park, Tunisia
6 year old female lion, born in spring, tan color, 300 pounds, from Zanzibar, Tanzania
